Okay, so let's summarize
everything we've learned about deployment on AWS.
So first CloudFormation, which is an AWS-only tool,
which is allowing you to do Infrastructure as Code
and works with almost all types of AWS resources.
This allows you to create templates,
and these templates can be used
to deploy infrastructure on AWS
and to use these templates across different Regions
and accounts to make your infrastructure truly repeatable.
Then we have Beanstalk, which is, again, AWS-only,
So Elastic Beanstalk,
which is a Platform as a Service or PaaS,
and it's limited to certain programming languages or Docker.
You can deploy your code consistently
with a known architecture, for example,
using the combination of a load balancer, EC2 instances,
and an RDS database.
CodeDeploy is to deploy
and upgrade any applications onto servers,
and this can be done on AWS,
for example, your EC2 instances,
but also it can be done on your on-premises infrastructure.
And this is why it's called
a hybrid type of service.
Systems Manager, yet again,
is a hybrid type of service,
which allows you to patch, configure,
and run commands at scale across all your servers.
So that's for all the deployment services,
but now let's talk about the developer services.
We've learned about CodeCommit,
which does come up in the exam,
which is to store code in a private Git repository,
giving you a version-controlled code repo,
CodeBuild, which is allowing you to build
and test your code in AWS in a serverless fashion,
CodeDeploy, which is allowing you
to deploy code onto servers,
so I bundle it both into the deployment
and the developer services
because they go along,
CodePipeline to do the orchestration
of a pipeline within AWS,
so from your code to your build, to your test,
your deployment, and your provisioning and so on,
CodeArtifacts to store software packages
and dependencies on AWS,
and then we have the CDK
to define your cloud infrastructure
using a programming language,
for example, JavaScript, TypeScript,
Java, Python, et cetera.
And this gets compiled into a CloudFormation template.
So that's it.
I hope you liked it,
and I will see you in the next section.